<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<reviews>
    <review id="41445647">
        <name>Peter B</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>10 Jan 2018</displaydate>
        <textcomments>....Gatorvac is awesome.   They replaced my central vacuum unit a year ago and troubleshot a broken outlet wire in the attic at the same time.   Their prices are fair, and they show up on time. recently one of my pvc vacuum lines came off, and I was getting low suction.   Robert spent a half hour on the phone troubleshooting the problem with me, no charge.   honest, old school business.  Rare to see anymore.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/41445647</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="40242049">
        <name>Ellen K</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>12 Dec 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Have purchased and serviced  my Miele vacuum cleaner at Gator.  In fact, this is the second one I bought from them. They are very knowledgeable and carry bags, hepa filters and anything else you may need.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/40242049</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="39857959">
        <name>Linda</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>05 Dec 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I have an old featherweight Singer machine that I can't trust to just anyone.  It's a simple, wonderful machine and it broke...

I took it to Gator Vac and Sewing and it was back home in just a few days, in better condition than it was before it broke.  It's been working like a charm ever since.  

I am so thankful for this business and their expertise!!!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/39857959</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="38863209">
        <name>Anonymous Customer</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>16 Nov 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Joey &amp; Ben did an excellent job upgrading our central vaccum system as part of a renovation.  Looks and works like a gem thanks to the professionalism and personal caring of these great guys.  Highly recommend.  Responsive, professional and great products...</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/38863209</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="38700592">
        <name>Michael</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>13 Nov 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Wow! I called and explain that my whole house vacuum system would not work. They said they would send a technician out in about two hours. Joe and Ben showed up within two hours, diagnosed the unit and found that the motor on the 10 year old unit was fried. They had units on the truck with them and I was able to choose a replacement unit that fit my needs perfectly. They removed the old unit installed the new one and I was up and running in about thirty minutes. The technicians were friendly, polite , honest and knowledgeable. It doesn't get any better than this. Gator Vacuum is my new best friend!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/38700592</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="36538198">
        <name>Jay</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>28 Sep 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I came to Gator Vacuum for a repair and the owner was excellent and gave me an honest overview of the vacuum I brought in. Suggested different models that would do what I needed for my Condo. Knowing the brand I most prefer that he sold I looked to purchase a new model. He suggested based on my actual needs, to consider one of the used reconditioned models of my brand preference. Perfect! A savings for me even though a lesser purchase price sale for Gator. Just took the unit in for the recommended servicing to keep it optimal.

The very best in honest service!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/36538198</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="33913143">
        <name>Nadine H</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>24 Jul 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Don't settle for less....When you can have THE BEST!!!!!!

            Now is the age of mega department stores, and mediocre service and just "ok" quality products.

            But if you want commitment to excellent customer service and a dedication to top of the line inventory you need to come meet Robert and his mom Phyllis. The owners for decades of Gator Vac &amp; Sewing in Coral Springs.

            For nearly 20 years Robert and his staff "lovingly" took care of my Miele Vacuum. He will know you and he will certainly knows what will fit your needs at any given time. The service is personal and friendly and his lines of superior cleaning have a reputation for excellence that can not be matched be matched by the come and go super stores of today.

            Do yourself a great service and drop by-- Meet their team and learn about what truly will make your life easier and healthier. They are the best, and you can forget the rest.



                Sincerely Yours,

                         Nadine Hankin

                         1200 NW 80th Ave

                         Apt 104

                         Margate, FL 33063</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/33913143</fullurl>
        <orderid>9545924206</orderid>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="32639035">
        <name>Patti's S</name>
        <displaydate>18 Jun 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I have had my 45-year-old Singer sewing machine serviced twice at Gator...once for cleaning and, just  recently, for a repair and complete overhaul. Both times my machine has come back sewing like new. I feel fortunate to have a place like Gator to service my machine.  They don't make them like they used to and I want to keep this one as long as I can. I just hope they are around as long as my machine!!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/32639035</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="30597180">
        <name>Ken M</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>21 Apr 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Recently realized while trying to vacuum myself, not done for a long while that 15 year old Sanitaire Commercial heavy duty upright that had magnets in front to catch staples and paper clips used to use in office, had torn bag and broken belt. Tried cleaning and fixing myself after finding replacement belt had in a box. After doing this and saw rollers tight tried it and in a minute or so belt broke. So fortunately found Gator on line took the Sanitaire and Eureka Mighty Mite for bag and tools to great store and Robert totally refurbished Sanitaire at reasonable price and both vacuums working great and like new  Ken Meyer Tamarac</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/30597180</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="27403044">
        <name>Steve E</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>13 Jan 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Gator Vacuum is the best local supply store for vacuum needs.  Their staff are super friendly and knowledgeable and eager to assist.  I cannot say enough about them, they are truly the best.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/27403044</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="27162170">
        <name>Efrezer</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>04 Jan 2017</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great job fixing Dyson. Quick and affordable. Knowledgeable customer service.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/27162170</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="26184789">
        <name>Judy J</name>
        <displaydate>03 Dec 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I love Gator vacuum!  I have been going there for years. They are so knowledgable about all of their products. Sharon knows everything about the products. She is so friendly too.  I trust them completely. They service my vacuum every 6 mos. and should I ever need a new one, you can bet I will be getting one from there. They have so much wonderful inventory.  Check out gator vacuum. They are awesome!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/26184789</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="25068434">
        <name>Frank</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>27 Oct 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>My overall shopping experience was excellent.  Ben and Joe were running a little late, but they called, which I appreciated.  They diagnosed the problem (my central vac was overheating and turning off).  They showed me the damage done to the motor and recommended rebuilding the motor or getting a new central vacuum.  I opted for the new machine which they had on the truck.  The installation went smoothly and took less time than anticipated.  They were efficient and clean.  With so many accolades, why didn't I rate Gator Vac 5 stars?  The one negative, which basically isn't the fault of Gator Vac, is that I was unable to shop around.  I could not compare prices.  Whomever I called to come to my home would get the job. To call another company would cost me another service charge.  I choose to be optimistic and conclude that I made the right decision.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/25068434</fullurl>
        <Overall>4.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="24820356">
        <name>Dawn</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>18 Oct 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Once again, Gator Vacuum to the rescue!  A number of months ago, my PowerStar Optima Plus (central vac) decided to no longer work after a few weeks of acting "tempermental." I called a number of supposed repair facilities--including original installer--who each made clear they were more interested in selling me new vs. repairing my not very old existing system.  

Gator Vac sent a servicemen out--same day--who quickly performed a systems diagnosis; id'd "the problem"; &amp; made recommendations re appropriate overhaul procedures. End of day--my vacuum like brand new! 

Today, called around, looking for bags &amp; was told by 2 different companies that my vacuum was discontinued &amp; bags no longer available--would I like to consider a new vac system? 

Found Gator Vac's no. &amp; correct bags--plentiful supply--is now on the way to my house: No fuss/no muss--just GREAT service &amp; VERY PLEASANT/HELPFUL people.  Nice!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/24820356</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="23573250">
        <name>Marcia</name>
        <displaydate>02 Sep 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>This group is great,fair, and reasonably priced group! Highly recommend them!great people</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/23573250</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="23021835">
        <name>Linda W</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>13 Aug 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Wonderful people very knowledgeable, helpful and honest.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/23021835</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22844282">
        <name>MV</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>06 Aug 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Very efficient and professional.  They also were very friendly.  I recommend you use them for central Vaccuum needs.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22844282</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22843040">
        <name>Roy D</name>
        <location> - NY, United States</location>
        <justlocation>NY, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>06 Aug 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>We originally purchased our new vac from this company through Iris. And when we vacation in Florida, we stop in to get bags and any other accessories we need for home. Quick, easy and friendly. Will continue to come back.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22843040</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22842620">
        <name>Diane</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>06 Aug 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Airways great service</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22842620</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22826093">
        <name>Txjude</name>
        <displaydate>05 Aug 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Efficient and pleasant.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22826093</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22799053">
        <name>Carol</name>
        <displaydate>04 Aug 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I have been a patron of this business for many years. The service has always been consistently excellent. It is a pleasure doing business with this establishment.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22799053</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22642506">
        <name>Darlene</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>29 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Excellent customer service and very professional. Customer is always first which in this day and age is hard to find.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22642506</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22641376">
        <name>Alida</name>
        <location> - PR, United States</location>
        <justlocation>PR, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>29 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>6 years ago you fixed my old sewing machine and still works perfect. Now my daughter in law has problems with her vac cleaner...I told my daughter inlaw to come here because I know you will fix the vac cleaner.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22641376</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22506140">
        <name>Cheryl m</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>23 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Gator vacuum is a family owned business that cares about service and their customers.  Great products and great service.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22506140</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22483255">
        <name>Mike</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>22 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Very easy, the website provided all of the information needed to make the decision to come here.



Eevery thing I needed was in stock and the staff had great sugestions.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22483255</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22438973">
        <name>L E</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>20 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Been coming to Gator for 20 years they always have taken good care of us</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22438973</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22256815">
        <name>Susan </name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>12 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I highly recommend Gator Vacuum.  They have provided excellent service and always do a great job at servicing my vacuum.  - Susan H.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22256815</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22260171">
        <name>Susie D</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>12 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great "service with a smile"!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22260171</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22188898">
        <name>HL</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>09 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great overall experience. Staff took time to explain problem and was bery flexible with pricing. Great overall experience. Highly recommended.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22188898</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22187228">
        <name>Jan</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>09 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>We have had a long relationship with this company and always is satisfactory. They know how to take care of all things that 

Have to do with vaccums.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22187228</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22172186">
        <name>Laura</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>08 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Love my vacuum</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22172186</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22166817">
        <name>Nina </name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>08 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Pleasant and professional. Job completed in a timely manner. Pleased with service</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22166817</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22165910">
        <name>Kathy h</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>08 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Excellent service . Sharon was very  knowledgeable and helpful in my service needs. Highly recommend Gator vacuum . I have been a customer for 23 years.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22165910</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22149142">
        <name>Linda </name>
        <location> - GA, United States</location>
        <justlocation>GA, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>07 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great experience, customer service &amp; time spent with us was above &amp; beyond.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22149142</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22148330">
        <name>Michele</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>07 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Excellent advise and products!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22148330</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="22018966">
        <name>Deluxe C</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>01 Jul 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>As always the best equipment for less, great people. Great selection. I wouid not go any where else. The best.  :)</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/22018966</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21870110">
        <name>Betsy</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>25 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I love these guys! They had me serviced in an hour! Plus they always remember me by name!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21870110</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21853564">
        <name>Iris</name>
        <displaydate>24 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great service, vacuum looked better than when I purchased it! Helpful staff and so quickly done. Highly Recommend them!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21853564</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21853345">
        <name>Heather</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>24 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great service. Very helpful staff.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21853345</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21854639">
        <name>Bill G</name>
        <displaydate>24 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great staff, Great selection got the vacuum my wife wanted was in and out in no time!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21854639</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21853646">
        <name>Fran stern </name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>24 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>I got great service at gator vacuum for my Miele and I can not wait to come back for my service!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21853646</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21619763">
        <name>Anonymous Customer</name>
        <displaydate>14 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great products and wonderful service!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21619763</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21618912">
        <name>Lisa S</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>14 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Happy my sewing machine was fixed quickly and was reasonable! Thanks.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21618912</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="21439996">
        <name>Anonymous Customer</name>
        <displaydate>06 Jun 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Sharon in the office was very accommodating. 

The staff that installed the vacuums were professional and very knowledgeable.  

Thank you both for making this an easy and enjoyable purchase.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/21439996</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="20370214">
        <name>Jo</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>23 Apr 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>The always provide great service, I great place to do business.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/20370214</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="20303441">
        <name>Jon</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>20 Apr 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Really great people.  They installed our central vac a couple of years ago.  The vac is fine and when I have  called for service or a problem Sharon has always tried to solve it over the phone so as to avoid service charges.  I had to replace the hose since it got an unfixable clog.  They tried clearing it but couldn't either.  They gave me a new one for a very good price.  They take very good care of their customers.  Highly recommended!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/20303441</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="20042004">
        <name>Shari</name>
        <displaydate>09 Apr 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great service great people, great vacuums</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/20042004</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="19972477">
        <name>Lynn</name>
        <displaydate>06 Apr 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>These folks really know household products!  They are well stocked and very up to date on every vacuum, vacuum parts.  I did not know there were so many useful and practical attachments for my old central vacuum!  I am so excited to use my new attachments and my house will be fresh and clean.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/19972477</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="19915795">
        <name>Anonymous Customer</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>04 Apr 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Always very helpful. Love the service!! Staff is ALWAYS a pleasure!!!!</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/19915795</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="19848761">
        <name>Deluxe Professional Cleaning S</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>01 Apr 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Really nice knowledgable sales staff. Great selection. Well organized.</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/19848761</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
    <review id="18318544">
        <name>jeff</name>
        <location> - FL, United States</location>
        <justlocation>FL, United States</justlocation>
        <displaydate>01 Feb 2016</displaydate>
        <textcomments>Great Store Great Service Great Vacuums</textcomments>
        <fullurl>http://www.shopperapproved.com/customer-review/Gator Vacuum &amp;amp; Sewing Co/18318544</fullurl>
        <Overall>5.0</Overall>
        <public>true</public>
        <verified>true</verified>
    </review>
</reviews>